thepensionsregulator.gov.uk 2010-11-24

# Privacy policy | The Pensions Regulator

### Site usage information

The Pensions Regulator uses a web analytics tool from Nedstat to measure and analyse information about the use of this website.

The analytics tool uses cookies and page tagging code to provide statistical information about visits to pages, number of documents downloaded, the route that visitors navigate through the site and other information relating to usage of this website including the IP address of visitors and data about your browser type and computer. The information gathered does not contain any personal information about you.

This information is gathered on behalf of the regulator by Nedstat, an independent measurement and research company.

The regulator's web communications team uses the information provided by Nedstat to make informed decisions about future website developments.

Further information about Nedstat, including Nedstat's privacy policy, is available at <http://www.nedstat.com/>

Additionally, we are currently using Google analytics on selected pages of our website. Google's pivacy policy is available at [www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

### More about cookies

A cookie is a small file that contains a unique, anonymous number. It does not contain any personal information. A cookie is stored on your computer when you visit a website and is used to recognise any repeat visits that you make to that site. The cookie cannot be used to identify you on websites of third parties.

It is possible to configure your web browser to refuse cookies or to be informed if a cookie is set. Please refer to your web browser help files for instructions.

### Log files

The regulator's web communications team periodically analyses the log files for this website. Log files contain data about visitor's use of this website, including IP addresses. Log files do not contain any personal information about you.

#### Email alerts

If you subscribe to our news-by-email service your email address will be recorded and stored. We will treat this as proprietary and confidential. You can unsubscribe from this service at any time at which time your email address will be deleted from our news-by-email database.
